cavsi.com 2008-12-17

# CAVSI, Email Privacy Policy

**February 29, 2008**

At CAVSI we recognize that privacy is important. We value our customers' trust and respect your privacy. We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**Why did you receive an email from us?**

If you received a mailing from us, your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future, or you have registered or have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. 

**What types of personal information we collect?**

This site does not offer the ability for users to submit personal data. No Personal Data Collected at This Site. 

This site uses Google Analytics for website analysis, which includes the recording and processing of such information as how your browser navigates this site and what keywords drove traffic to this site. Google Analytics utilizes both cookies and web beacons. "Cookies" are small text files that contain a string of alpha-numeric characters and are used to associate an action taken by a browser with subsequent actions taken by that browser. Web beacons are small strings of HTML code that are placed in a Web page, and are sometimes called "clear GIFs" (Graphics Interchange Format) or "pixel tags." Web beacons are most often used in conjunction with cookies. 

**How we use and share personal information?**

We do not share, sells, or rents your email address or personal information with other companies. CAVSI only will share personal information with its subsidiaries or if CAVSI becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, insolvency, or asset sale. 

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. 

To remove your name from our marketing lists, please follow the instructions noted below: 

. Click on the " **unsubscribe** " link located in all of our promotional emails. 

. Send a blank email to [unsuscribe@promo.cavsi.com](mailto:unsuscribe@promo.cavsi.com)

**Note:** Requests to opt out of promotional e-mails will be honored within **10** business days. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This website may contain links to other sites, such as commercial ads located in pages that offers free information. 

**Changes to this policy**

CAVSI may change its privacy policy or practices from time to time. We will post the most current version of our privacy policy online at www.cavsi.com/english/PrivacyPolicy.html

**Questions Regarding Privacy**

If you have further questions or concerns relating to this site's privacy practices, please email [PrivacyQuestions@promo.cavsi.com](mailto:PrivacyQuestions@promo.cavsi.com), feel free to contact us through this web site, call us at **305-407-8472** / **407-803-1229** , or write us at:

**CAVSI  
1825 W 44th Place   
Hialeah   
Florida, 33012   
USA**
